ADAM MINKUS

Seattle, WA 98105

847-826-0121 <u>adam.minkus@gmail.com</u>

OPERATIONS MANAGEMENT

Analyze, Improve, and Implement Manufacturing Processes

Experience in process and operation management, resource scheduling, and compliance regulation. Outstanding communicator who possess an enthusiastic and positive demeanor with unrelenting vigilance and passion in delivering on-time results and meeting company needs.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SATURN GROUP, Bellevue, WA March 2018 to September 2018

Director of Cultivation

- Create operating plans and resource scheduling for a complex indoor agricultural manufacturing facility
- Identify and implement improvements to operation management by analyzing current processes and incorporating large scale agricultural practices to maximize resources and optimize the manufacturing operations
- Discuss and analyze newly incorporated improvements with team to maximize resources
- Responsible for the timely procurement of all production materials
- Managed cultivation team to ensure all staff members understood correct procedures and practices which in turn increased uniformity in operations
- Developed and launched new production method that resulted in increased yield by 300% with decreased inputs
- Developed the documentation of these improved processes to ensure day in and day out consistency

PLANT HEALTH CARE, INC, Seattle, WA 2016 to 2018

Research Associate II

- Responsible for the management of all bio assay operations ensuring the team met yearly goals
- Responsible for all project management within bioassay group
- Identified and implemented improvements to production methodologies
- Kept detailed records of all assays performed along with the results, organizing them and presenting them to upper management to demonstrate product progression and development
- Developed resource scheduling spreadsheets to optimize bioassay team activities
- In cooperation with peptide engineer, utilized results from assays to make recommendations to help guide assay development as well as field trials

CE GROUP, Bellingham, WA 2014 - 2016

Cultivation Manager

- Created complex production plans and performed resource scheduling of all processes organized by daily, weekly, and monthly needs.
- Performed, evaluated, and documented experiments comparing differing processes, equipment, and design layout. I then presented suggestions for improvements to managing partner.
- Responsible for the operation management of a seven day a week production facility.
- Generated documentation methods to ensure smooth workflow and uniformity in final product.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (BS), Environmental Horticulture Science CALIFORNIA POLYTECHNIC STATE UNIVERSITY, San Luis Obispo, CA.